Somebody That I Used To Know
压制:随Feng
歌手：Gotye ft & Kimbra
Now and then I think of when we were together
偶尔想起那一起的日子
Like when you said you felt so happy you could die
仿佛还是你快乐至极的时刻
Told myself that you were right for me
告诉自己 你就是我想要的
But felt so lonely in your company
可是有了你的陪伴 并没有减少我的孤单
But that was love and it's an ache I still remember
那就是爱 就是那忘不掉的疼
You can get addicted to a certain kind of sadness
对于某个伤痛都会沉迷的你
Like resignation to the end
最后却好像无可奈何
Always the end
总是这样到最后
So when we found that we could not make sense
所以当我们感情也平淡的时候
Well you said that we would still be friends
你会说我们还是朋友吧
But I'll admit that I was glad that it was over
我承认我愿意结束这样的感情
But you didn't have to cut me off
可是你不必这样远离我
Make out like it never happened
好像我们曾经什么也没有过
And that we were nothing
好像我们从不曾来过
And I don't even need your love
我甚至可以不需要你的爱
But you treat me like a stranger
可是你却视我如路人
And that feels so rough
我是如此难过
You didn't have to stoop so low
你不必如此躲开我
Have your friends collect your records
你的朋友整理了你的讯息了么
And then change your number
改变了你的号码了么
I guess that I don't need that though
我想我不必在有这样那样的想法了
Now you're just somebody that I used to know
现在的你只是我曾经认识的某某而已
Now and then I think of all the times you screwed me over
偶尔想起所有缠绵的日子
But had me believing it was always something that I'd done
可是让我相信的我们曾经的事 也只有它
And I don't wanna live that way
我不想再要那样的生活
Reading into every word you say
看穿你说的每句话
You said that you could let it go
你说你可以放手
And I wouldn't catch you hung up on somebody that you used to know...
我不会再看到你徘徊在你曾经的过去
But you didn't have to cut me off
可是你不必这样远离我
Make out like it never happened
好像我们曾经什么也没有过
And that we were nothing
好像我们从不曾来过
And I don't even need your love
我甚至可以不需要你的爱
But you treat me like a stranger
可是你却视我如路人
And that feels so rough
我是如此难过
You didn't have to stoop so low
你不必如此躲开我
Have your friends collect your records
你的朋友整理了你的讯息了么
And then change your number
改变了你的号码了么
I guess that I don't need that though
我想我不必在有这样那样的想法了
Now you're just somebody that I used to know
现在的你只是我曾经认识的某某而已
Somebody
某某
I used to know
我曾经认识
Somebody that I used to know
我曾经认识的某某而已
压制:随Feng
I used to know
我曾经认识的
Somebody...
某某